Since we're looking for this embryonic power,
既然我们要寻找这种胚胎力量，
we must align ourselves with this embryonic power.
我们就必须与这种胚胎力量同频。
It's like a radio frequency, you see, where I'm looking for that frequency.
这就像收音机频率，你明白吗，我正在寻找那个频率。
For this, we will learn to observe the patient's breathing.
为此，我们将学习观察患者的呼吸。
Really observe it, the patient's first breath.
真正地观察，患者的第一次呼吸。
And little by little, we will look for a point, a door,
然后慢慢地，我们将寻找一个点，一扇门，
where we will deposit our sensation.
我们将把我们的感觉放在那里。
which is at the end of the exhale and before the inhale.
那是在呼气结束和吸气之前。
Let's do this exercise together already to simply discover a quality of the mind.
让我们一起做这个练习，只是为了简单地发现一种精神品质。
You will all join me.
你们都会和我一起好好地做。
You will connect with my gaze.
你们会与我的目光连接。
I'm taking you all in.
我把你们都带上。
And we're simply going to take an inhale together.
我们只是简单地一起吸气。
And we exhale.
然后呼气。
we inhale
我们吸气
we exhale
我们呼气
we follow the exhalation
我们跟随呼气
and at the end of the exhale
在呼气结束时
we will slightly prolong
我们将稍微延长
the short apnea
短暂的屏息
we will do it voluntarily
我们将有意识地这样做
we inhale together
我们一起吸气
you stay in this state
你保持在这个状态
and you re-inhale
然后你再次吸气
if you lose it, you exhale again
如果你失去了它，你再次呼气
you observe
你观察
you re-inhale
你再次吸气
and you stay in this state
你保持在这个状态
you might observe
你也许可以观察到
we go into this end of exhale
我们进入呼气末期
it's like something is suspended a bit
就好像有什么东西稍微悬浮了一下
very gently
非常缓慢地
and if you observe, thoughts suddenly
如果你观察，思绪突然间
slow down
慢了下来
in fact, there's a tissue quality
事实上，有一种组织品质
a quality of mind that appears
一种精神品质出现了
that means that in that quality
这意味着在这种品质中
it's in that quality
正是在这种品质中
that we're going to start working
我们将开始工作
okay, it's there
好的，就是这里
you'll see that other perceptions will arrive
你会看到有其他的感知出现
okay
好的
so for that
所以为此
be very attentive
要非常专注
to the breathing
在呼吸上
I simply observe
我只是观察
I observe the changes
我观察变化
but when this state appears
但当这种状态出现时
even if there's an inhalation
即使有吸气
we can stay
我们也可以保持
in this sensation
在这种感觉中
it's always there
它总是在那里
you can continue it
你可以继续它
like a door opening at that moment
就像一扇门在那一刻打开
and you can go all the way in
你可以完全投入其中
let's do it again together
我们再做一次，通过
you connect well
你们好好连接
with the spirit
与精神
of that one
与他的精神
he's always in it
他一直都在里面
so you inhale
就这样你吸气
now we're going to do it
现在我们要这样做
we're going to complicate it a little bit
我们要稍微复杂一点
we're not going to take a voluntary breath
就是我们不做自主呼吸
We're going to observe our normal breathing and you're just going to be
我们将观察我们的正常呼吸，你只需
attentive to
注意将自己
settle into this space. Keep your eyes open, stay
安放在这个空间里。睁开眼睛，留在这里，
with me, here, fix your gaze
和我在一起，在这里，凝视那里
on this gentleman's eyes. Inhale,
这位先生的眼神。吸气，
observe your breathing.
观察你的呼吸。
Then we exhale.
然后我们呼气。
When we exhale,
当我们呼气时，
at the end of the exhalation,
在呼气结束时，
a small door opens.
有一扇小门打开。
You settle there,
你把自己安放在那里，
like a child sitting down.
就像一个孩子坐下一样。
Thoracic breathing
胸式呼吸
is truly triggered at the moment of birth.
真正在出生时启动。
The opening before.
之前的开放。
makes small diaphragmatic movements,
做一些小的膈肌运动，
but it's not yet.
但这还不是。
That means the breath of life
这意味着生命的气息
is before that moment.
在此之前就已经存在了。
And so, when we enter there,
所以，当我们进入那里时，
we will seek to work on the breath.
我们将努力呼吸。
And there, it's an entry point
这是一个入口，
to, I'm giving you a key,
我给你一个线索，
to enter into this perception of the breath.
让你进入对呼吸的感知。
After that, we'll go even further.
之后，我们还会走得更远。
Because after that, we'll look for
因为之后，我们将寻找
the balance points in primary respiration
原发性呼吸中的平衡点
to find the points of silence
以找到寂静点
or the problem of emotion.
或情绪问题。
intelligence can resurface in the pathways of transformation.
智慧可以在转化途径中重新浮现。